[{"answer": "Hello", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 17, "question": "", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Hi, Gretchen.  Its Dave", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Hello", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Hi, Dave.  How are you", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Hi, Gretchen.  Its Dave", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Im pretty good.  How about you", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Hi, Dave.  How are you", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Im doing great.  The weather heres been so nice lately.  Whats it like up i", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Im pretty good.  How about you", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Its freezing", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Im doing great.  The weather heres been so nice lately.  Whats it like up i", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " As usual.  So, whats new", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Its freezing", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Well, Ive decided to go to grad school somewhere in the States next year", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 27, "question": " As usual.  So, whats new", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Thats great news.  I think that youll really be happy that you came to stud", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Well, Ive decided to go to grad school somewhere in the States next year", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " No, not yet.  Im still kind of in the beginning stages of the process", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Thats great news.  I think that youll really be happy that you came to stud", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " You have a while to decide still", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " No, not yet.  Im still kind of in the beginning stages of the process", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yeah.  I wanted to ask you some questions about the applications for th", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 37, "question": " You have a while to decide still", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Sure.  You can ask me anything", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yeah.  I wanted to ask you some questions about the applications for th", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Well, what is included in the application", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Sure.  You can ask me anything", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " You know, every university has different admission requirements, so yo", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Well, what is included in the application", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Oh, OK", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " You know, every university has different admission requirements, so yo", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " But, I can give you an idea of the general things that are usually required", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Oh, OK", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Oh, that would be great", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 50, "question": " But, I can give you an idea of the general things that are usually required", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " First, theres the application itself, obviously.  Also, you often need to writ", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Oh, that would be great", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " What kind of essay", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 55, "question": " First, theres the application itself, obviously.  Also, you often need to writ", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Why you want to go to the school, why they should choose you, you", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 56, "question": " What kind of essay", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " What else", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Why you want to go to the school, why they should choose you, you", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " You usually need your test scores on the GRE and TOEFL, a copy of you", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 61, "question": " What else", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Thats a piece of cake.  English is my first language, so I dont need to take th", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 65, "question": " You usually need your test scores on the GRE and TOEFL, a copy of you", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Its a little more complicated.  Since you didnt go to an American high schoo", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Thats a piece of cake.  English is my first language, so I dont need to take th", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Whats that for", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Its a little more complicated.  Since you didnt go to an American high schoo", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " The evaluation companies basically just tell the U.S. universities how man", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Whats that for", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " That seems like a major pain", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 82, "question": " The evaluation companies basically just tell the U.S. universities how man", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " It is, but without that they cant read your transcripts and they wont accep", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 83, "question": " That seems like a major pain", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Is that all Ill need", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 87, "question": " It is, but without that they cant read your transcripts and they wont accep", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Sometimes therere a few more things like your resume, an", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Is that all Ill need", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Yeah, Ill do that this month.  Listen, thanks for helping me out with all of this.  Il", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Sometimes therere a few more things like your resume, an", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Yes, keep me posted and good luck", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Yeah, Ill do that this month.  Listen, thanks for helping me out with all of this.  Il", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Thanks.  Bye", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Yes, keep me posted and good luck", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "04-04", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Thanks.  Bye", "qSentId": 99}]
